[{
        "Question": "Select question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
    },{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": "A red loc_a location is below the red block. An orange loc_b location is below the orange block. A blue loc_f location is below the blue block. A loc_c location is below the green block. A yellow loc_d location is below the yellow block. A red block is on the red loc_a location. An orange block is on the orange loc_b location. A blue block is on the blue loc_f location. A green block is on the loc_c location. A yellow block is on the yellow loc_d location. "
    },{
        "Question": "What is 'matched'?",
        "Answer": "If the color of an object is the color of a block and the block is on the object, then it is matched."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is on the red location 6?",
        "Answer": "A red block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is on the orange location 7?",
        "Answer": "An orange block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is on the location 8?",
        "Answer": "A green block."
    }, {
        "Question": "What is on the yellow location 9?",
        "Answer": "A yellow block"
    }, {
        "Question": "What is on the green location 10?",
        "Answer": "Nothing."
    },{
        "Question": "What is on the blue location 11?",
        "Answer": "A blue block."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the red block 1?",
        "Answer": "A red loc_a location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the orange block 2?",
        "Answer": "An orange loc_b location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the green block 4?",
        "Answer": "A loc_c location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the yellow block 3?",
        "Answer": "A yellow loc_d location."
    },{
        "Question": "What is below the blue block 5?",
        "Answer": "A blue loc_f location."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the red location 6?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is red. A red block is on the red loc_a location."
    }, {
        "Question": "Describe the orange location 7?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is orange. An orange block is on the orange loc_b location. "
    }, {
        "Question": "Describe the location 8?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. A green block is on the loc_c location."
    }, {
        "Question": "Describe the yellow location 9?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is yellow. A yellow block is on the yellow loc_d location."
    }, {
        "Question": "Describe the green location 10?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is green."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the blue location 11?",
        "Answer": "The shape is location. The color is blue. A blue block is on the blue loc_f location."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the red block 1?",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is red. A red loc_a location is below the red block."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the orange block 2?",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is orange. An orange loc_b location is below the orange block."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the green block 4?",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is green. A loc_c location is below the green block."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the yellow block 3?",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is yellow. A yellow loc_d location is below the yellow block."
    },{
        "Question": "Describe the blue block 5?",
        "Answer": "The shape is block. The color is blue. A blue loc_f location is below the blue block."
    }
]

